# **Envi Bagus Aditya**

### **UI/UX** Designer

Envi is a highly skilled and motivated UI/UX Designer with a passion for digital products. I bring creative design skills and technical expertise to my projects to make intuitive user-centered designs. Have experience working with teams to analyze and create beautiful product design based on requirements and design thinking process using atomic design approach. I am constantly exploring new technologies and design trends, also have some front-end coding experiences.

### Experience



NATIVE PRODUCTIONS • April 2022 - Present

Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed low-fidelities and high-fidelities for multiple projects in company correlated with Web2 and Web3.
- > Conducted UX research and interview on several projects from start to
- > Coded landing pages website projects using HTML, CSS, Javascript for client projects



AIRDROP VENTURES PTE. LTD. • September 2022 - January 2023

UI/UX Designer

Full-time - Semi Remote Singapore

- > Designed and Collaborated with teams in total 3 big projects correlated with Web3 from Low-fidelity into High-fidelity
- > Organised and Built company complex design system for multiple products in Company.
- > UX Researched base requirements and regulation in Indonesia for building products.
- > Directed other UX/UI Designer to maximise workflow in Figma in a tight deadlines utilising Plugins, Shortcuts, Libraries, and Design System.



PT. IDOOH BERSAMA INDOESIA • June 2022 - October 2022

**UI/UX** Designer

- > Designed and Prototyped multiple products following Tailwind UI style guides.
- > Conducted UX Audit some of other products that the company have launch and currently build.
- > Directed 3 UI/UX Designers on teams to maximise the workflow for faster project done.
- > Created complex design system for products and company.
- > Conducted user interview for every new projects, Created user flows, mind map, wireframes, information architecture.



MERGED, INC. • June 2022 - Nov 2022

Freelance UI/UX Designer

Part-time - Remote Ocalifornia

- > Conducted research about most popular payment banking and payment system in the United States.
- > Designed mobile low-fidelity, design system, and high-fidelity of Merged
- > Building prototypes, brand guides to be used for pitching and marketing purposes.
- > Created design system for product source of truth



PT. TIGA TOKEN DIGITAL • June 2021 - September 2022

**UI/UX Designer** 

Full-time • Bali, Indonesia

- > Designed 6+ big projects related to Web3 including NFT Marketplace, Crypto Wallet Extension, Crypto Exchange, Staking, and Crypto Launchpad as a single UX/UI Designer in company
- > Designed NEFTiPEDiA NFT Marketplace as a main product of company resulted 15,000 Downloaders IOS and Android
- > Coded multiple landing pages for each company website products using HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- > Conducted research about Web3 and Blockchain in designer role.
- > Created graphic design for various events and social media purposes.



PT. LABELLE PELARIAN INDONESIA Sep - 2019- Nov 2019

**Product Designer** 

Full-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed and Managed versioning of Travel agent website app and Community traveling platform that focusing on women using Figma.
- > Conducted UX Research related to the travel agent product
- > Managed website using Docker and Linux.



VENTRAPEDIA • July 2019- Dec 2020

Freelance Web Designer Part-time Pali, Indonesia

- > Designed Responsive design of Travel agent website app and Community Platform using Adobe XD.
- > Designed dashboard for managing travel platform.
- > Coded all the design using HTML, CSS, Javascript with Bootstrap and Bulma Frameworks.



**PT. LUMONATA** • Aug 2017 - Oct 2017

**Web Designer** 

Internship • Bali, Indonesia

- > Focused learning Web design and Web development with teams.
- > Created some graphic designs using Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator.
- > Participated in multiple website design competitions.
- > Helped some designs and development for the company

#### Contact

Portfolio Website envibagus.netlify.app



linkedin.com/in/envibagus

+62 878 6222 0311

envibagus@gmail.com

Location

Bali, Indonesia

### Skills

#### Design

Visual Design **Design Thinking** · Mobile Design **UX Research**  Web Design **UX** Writing · SAAS Design

Interaction Design Design System Design Principle · Design Tokens

Prototyping · Figma Libraries

#### **Tools**

#### Fiama

Figma Expert - Able to fully maximise features of Figma with plugins, shortcuts, hidden features, and multiple tricks to accelerate workflow for project done.

Zeplin Figjam Miro Invision Framer Maze **ProtoPie** Notion Sketch Linear

Adobe XD Google Workspace **Adobe Illustrator** Microsoft 365 Adobe Photoshop Atlassian Products

**Soft Skills** 

**Problem Solving** Project Management Leadership Attention to detail Collaboration **Public Speaking** Adaptability

Development

**SQL** Database HTML & CSS Javascript **Bootstrap Version Control** Tailwind CSS

### **Certification & Awards**

Bootcamp UI/UX & Product Management Harisenin.com Bootcamp • January 2023

Design Thinking Techniques for Efficiency Binar Academy • September 2022

**UX Design for Product Development** Skill Academy • March 2020

3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2020 Stiki Indonesia • February 2020 2nd Winner of National Group Web design

Universitas Bunda Mulia, Jakarta · April 2019

3rd Winner of Web design Paras ICT 2019

Stiki Indonesia • February 2019 1st Winner of Web design PNBWDC

Politeknik Negeri Bali • September 2018 2nd Winner of National Web design Invention

Universitas Udayana • June 2018

# **Education**

Harisenin.com

Bootcamp Product Management and UI/UX

August 2022 - January 2023

ITB Stikom Bali

Bachelor Degree in Information System

September 2019 - Present

SMK TI Bali Global

Vocational High school majoring in Software Engineering

July 2016 - July 2019

# Languages

Indonesian

Native or bilingual proficiency

Professional working proficiency

Envi Bagus Aditya